{
    "id": "8e2a8a3452194dd1b5cd14f9c5dbd515",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The cat is inferior …………….. the dog in intelligence.",
            "description": "Inferior is followed by to instead of than.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When the journalists protested, the minister made no ………………. comments.",
            "description": "Further means additional.",
            "answers": [
                "farther",
                "further",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Chennai is ………………. from Mumbai than Bangalore.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "farther",
                "further",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahim is senior …………….. all other teachers in the school.",
            "description": "Senior is followed by to instead of than.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you give me ………………. rice, please?",
            "description": "We use some in affirmative sentences and any in negative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. knowledge is a dangerous thing.",
            "description": "A little means some. ",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "a little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… rice we have is enough to feed 10 persons.",
            "description": "The little means not much, but all that is there.",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… knowledge of mathematics that he possessed proved very useful.",
            "description": "The little means not much, but all that is there.",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "My cousin ………………… two daughters.",
            "description": "When have is used to talk about possessions or relationships, it is not used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "is having",
                "has",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Here ……………… our leader!",
            "description": "Even though an action is in progress at the time of speaking, present continuous tense is not used if it is an exclamatory sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "is coming",
                "comes",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}